Hello friends
안녕하세요 친구
Keep everyone waiting for a long time
다들 오래 기다리게 해주세요
I am Shiyan
나는 시얀이다
Everyone is welcome to attend
누구나 참석할 수 있습니다.
Mingyu Yunchuang press conference
민규 윤추앙 기자간담회
In the past few years, Shi Yan
지난 몇 년 동안 Shi Yan은
It can be considered prosperous.
번영했다고 볼 수 있습니다.
The Shi family and his son are really good.
Shi 가족과 그의 아들은 정말 좋습니다.
left at that time
그 때 떠났어
Shi Yan is missing a big burden
Shi Yan은 큰 부담을 놓치고 있습니다
The format of this press conference
이번 기자회견 형식
At first glance, it’s the young man’s idea
얼핏 보면 청년의 생각이다.
Satsuki
사츠키
are you uncomfortable
불편해?
I'm fine
잘 지내요
If you feel uncomfortable, tell me
불편하시면 말씀해주세요
Are you not used to it?
익숙하지 않은가?
this kind of scene
이런 장면
Feeling a little boring
조금 지루한 느낌
Mr. Shi always looks at me
Shi 선생님은 항상 나를 보십니다.
I'm a little scared
조금 무서워요
take it easy
진정해
He's looking at me
그 사람이 나를 보고 있어요
She's quite confident
그녀는 꽤 자신감이 있어요
This year
올해
Yunchuang also works with many
Yunchuang은 또한 많은 사람들과 협력합니다.
Join hands with new friends
새로운 친구들과 손을 잡고
these friends
이 친구들
All from new tracks
새로운 트랙의 모든 것
Have innovative spirit
혁신적 정신을 가지고 있다
and social responsibility
그리고 사회적 책임
You can look forward to it
기대하셔도 좋습니다
At this time, Yan was talking about Le'an, right?
이때 Yan은 Le'an에 대해 이야기하고 있었죠?
Mingyu Yunchuang invested this year
Mingyu Yunchuang은 올해 투자했습니다.
Many technology companies
많은 기술 회사
Technology companies are risky
기술 기업은 위험하다
Once this succeeds
일단 이게 성공하면
The return is very high
수익률이 매우 높네요
Shi Yan is very good
시얀은 아주 좋아
Recommend technical experts
기술 전문가 추천
with minimum capital
최소한의 자본으로
Get more shares
더 많은 공유를 받으세요
The fugitive prince Mingyu
도망친 왕자 민규
Something
무엇
The future life is terrible
미래의 삶은 끔찍하다
Sister Shuyi, I’m a little bored
슈이 언니, 나 좀 심심해요
Can I go out for some air?
나가서 바람 좀 쐬어도 될까요?
Go quickly and don't go too far
빨리 가되 너무 멀리 가지 말고
The press conference is halfway through
기자회견이 절반쯤 지났다.
give everyone some time
모두에게 시간을 좀 줘
Absorb and digest
흡수 및 소화
What we learned from the first half
전반전에서 배운 것
Also try us for everyone
또한 모두를 위해 우리를 시험해보십시오
Prepared refreshments
준비된 다과
See you in the second half for more content
하반기에 더 많은 콘텐츠로 만나요
he is on stage
그는 무대에 있어요
Still very charming
여전히 매우 매력적이다
Mr. Shi
시 씨
Hello Mr. Wang
안녕하세요 왕씨님
Are you a reporter from a financial agency?
금융기관 기자이신가요?
you are
당신은
I am a reporter from Jiangcheng Daily
저는 강성일보 기자입니다
I used to be there too
나도 거기 있었어
Financial agency internship
금융기관 인턴십
What a coincidence
이런 우연이
At that time, the leader of the special group
당시 특수그룹의 리더는
His name is Tang Yi, do you know him?
그 사람 이름은 Tang Yi인데, 그를 아시나요?
She is now my editor-in-chief
그녀는 이제 내 편집장이다
That's even more coincidental
그게 더 우연이네
My name is He Boming and you?
내 이름은 히보밍이고 당신은요?
My name is Zheng Shuyi
내 이름은 정수이(Zheng Shuyi)입니다.
Then let’s add WeChat
그럼 WeChat을 추가해 볼까요
We can communicate more in the future
앞으로도 더 많이 소통하겠습니다
sure
확신하는
Scan me
스캔해 주세요
I scan you
나는 당신을 스캔
Reporter Zheng Shuyi
정수이 기자
Please come over here
여기로 와주세요
He calls you over
그 사람이 당신에게 전화했어요
It turns out you guys know each other
알고보니 너희들은 서로 아는 사이였어
Shi Yan was jealous
시옌은 질투했다
He is sore
그는 아프다
Mr. Shi
시 씨
looking for me
나를 찾고
What do you want from me?
나한테서 뭘 원하는 거야?
you
너
Where is the female reporter next to me?
내 옆에 여자 기자는 어디 있지?
Came with you
너와 함께 왔어
that female reporter
그 여자 기자
Where have you gone?
어디 갔다?
call me over
나한테 전화해
It was to inquire about Qin Shiyue
진시월에 대해 문의하기 위해서였다.
He was really looking at Qin Shiyue just now
그는 지금 정말로 Qin Shiyue를보고있었습니다.
You look for her
당신은 그녀를 찾습니다
She just went out
그녀는 방금 나갔어
Do you need me to help you contact her?
그 사람에게 연락하는 데 제가 도움이 필요하신가요?
Don't pick up, don't pick up, don't pick up
받지 마세요, 받지 마세요, 받지 마세요
Completed Completed
완료 완료
Are you going to take me back so soon?
그렇게 빨리 나를 다시 데려갈 건가요?
Hey Xiaoyue, where are you?
샤오위에야, 어디야?
I'm in the lobby outside
나 지금 로비 밖에 있어
I didn't go far
나는 멀리 가지 않았다
Do you want me to go back?
내가 다시 돌아가길 바라나요?
you feel unwell
몸이 안 좋아
Already gone home
이미 집에 갔어
I didn't leave
나는 떠나지 않았다
no problem, no problem
문제 없어, 문제 없어
No need to bother
귀찮게 할 필요가 없습니다
No need to come back
돌아올 필요는 없어
Sister Shuyi, what are you talking about?
슈이 자매님, 무슨 말씀이세요?
Health is important
건강은 중요하다
take a good rest
잘 쉬다
Then I'll hang up
그럼 끊을게요
I
나
Boss Shi, she has already left
사장님, 그녀는 이미 떠났어요
Where have you gone?
어디 갔다?
What do you care about her?
당신은 그녀에 대해 무엇을 걱정합니까?
She felt unwell and went home
그녀는 몸이 안 좋아서 집에 갔다
What's wrong with her?
그녀에게 무슨 문제가 있나?
What does it have to do with you?
그게 당신과 무슨 관련이 있나요?
She has CEO phobia
그녀는 CEO 공포증이 있다
What
무엇
Just seeing a big shot like you
너 같은 거물을 보는 것만으로도
She will be out of breath
그녀는 숨이 차겠지
Chest tightness and shortness of breath
가슴이 답답하고 호흡이 가빠짐
I'm different
난 다른 해요
I feel happy when I see you
당신을 보면 기분이 좋아져요
jubilant, elated
기뻐하는, 의기양양한
Mr. Shi
시 씨
The second half begins
후반전이 시작됩니다
Did I get it?
내가 받았나요?
Cannon Fodder Female Supporting Script
대포 사료 여성 지원 스크립트
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Give me my coffee
내 커피 줘
thank you
감사합니다
An absolute blue chip stock.
절대적인 블루칩 주식.
No matter what happens, you won't lose anything.
무슨 일이 일어나더라도 아무것도 잃지 않을 것입니다.
The premise is
전제는
I can buy this stock
나는 이 주식을 살 수 있다
Welcome back
돌아온 것을 환영합니다
I will be there for you in the second half
하반기에도 내가 함께할게
Introducing some important figures in Yunchuang
Yunchuang의 주요 인물을 소개합니다.
partners and friends
파트너와 친구
Next
다음
I will announce a
나는
For Yunchuang
윈추앙(Yunchuang)의 경우
crucial
중대한
and significant news
그리고 중요한 소식
Kwan Capital
관캐피탈
Will formally inject capital into Mingyu Yunchuang
Mingyu Yunchuang에 공식적으로 자본을 투입할 예정입니다.
Become Mingyu Yunchuang
민규 윤추앙이 되어 보세요
important future partners
미래의 중요한 파트너
Next we invite
다음으로 초대합니다
Kwan Capital's
관캐피탈의
Strategic consultant Yu You took the stage
전략 컨설턴트 Yu You가 무대에 올랐습니다.
Looking ahead with everyone
모두와 함께 앞을 바라보며
The future of Yunchuang and Guanshi
Yunchuang과 Guanshi의 미래
Thank you Mr. Shi
감사합니다 미스터 시
Guan is determined to
구안은 결심한다.
Committed to innovation and talent introduction
혁신과 인재 도입에 전념
Future Kwan family
미래관가족
will also work with Yunchuang
Yunchuang과도 협력할 것입니다.
Continue to focus on technological innovation
계속해서 기술 혁신에 집중
under the power of the new economy
새로운 경제의 힘으로
Original financial model
원래 재무 모델
and the old interest pattern
그리고 예전의 관심 패턴
will be gradually broken
점차 깨질 것이다
Many companies are exploring
많은 기업들이 탐색 중
When innovating
혁신할 때
Easy to think rigidly
딱딱하게 생각하면 편하다
Can’t escape from own business
자기 사업에서 벗어날 수 없다
Looking at issues with the industry
업계 현안 살펴보니
It's him
그 사람이에요
It's an honor to join the Kwan family
관가족이 되신 것을 영광으로 생각합니다
Witness Guan’s breakthrough development
Guan의 획기적인 발전을 목격하세요
Also watch
또한 시청하세요
This is too blatant, right?
너무 노골적이죠?
thank you all for coming
와줘서 고마워요
Hope Mingyu Yunchuang
호프 민규 윤추앙
Join hands with Kwan Capital
관캐피탈과 손잡다
climb together
함께 오르다
Continue to write a new chapter
계속해서 새로운 장을 쓰세요
I announce this conference
이번 회의를 발표합니다
It ends here
여기서 끝
Mr. Shi
시 씨
Please post it
게시해주세요
Thoughts on this press conference
이번 기자회견에 대한 생각
Mr. Shi, what do you think of Yunchuang?
Shi 씨, Yunchuang에 대해 어떻게 생각하시나요?
What is the future investment direction?
향후 투자 방향은 무엇인가?
Sister Shuyi
슈이 자매
I have something to go
나 갈 일이 있어
that
저것
My company still has something to do
우리 회사는 아직 할 일이 있어
I'm leaving first
나 먼저 갈게
good
좋은
This conference
이번 컨퍼런스
I'm personally very satisfied
개인적으로 매우 만족합니다
Thank you too
나도 고마워요
Arrival of media friends
미디어 친구들의 도착
Do you have any questions?
질문있으세요?
you're done
넌 끝났어
just ended
방금 끝났어
Sister Shuyi, I want to ask
슈이 언니, 묻고 싶어요
Just now on stage
지금 막 무대에 있어
Who is the person who spoke?
말한 사람은 누구입니까?
Of course it's a seasonal banquet
물론 계절의 연회입니다
Didn't you wake up?
안 일어났어?
Why is it that both men and women
왜 남자와 여자 모두
I only have eyes for my little uncle
내 눈엔 작은 삼촌밖에 없어
Am I the only one who saw it?
저만 본 걸까요?
The other one is handsome
다른 하나는 잘생겼다
Another elegant speaker?
또 다른 우아한 스피커?
Qin Shiyue
진시웨
where are you not feeling well
어디 몸이 안 좋아?
I don't feel uncomfortable anywhere.
어디에서도 불편함을 느끼지 않습니다.
first press conference
첫 번째 기자회견
You just take advantage of it
넌 그냥 그걸 이용하면 돼
Qin Shiyue
진시웨
Are you itchy?
가렵나요?
Uncle, uncle, please let go first.
삼촌, 삼촌 먼저 놔주세요.
I know I'm wrong, okay?
나도 내가 틀렸다는 걸 알아, 알았지?
I think you want to go directly
직접 가보고 싶으신 것 같아요
Come and report here
여기로 와서 신고하세요
right
오른쪽
I don't dare anymore
더 이상 감히 할 수 없어
I will work hard
나는 열심히 일할 것이다
Never fish again
다시는 낚시하지 마세요
Uncle, please forgive me
삼촌, 용서해주세요
OK
좋아요
There are so many people
사람이 너무 많아서
Shiyan, you actually
시옌, 너 사실은
Picking up women in broad daylight
대낮에 여자를 데리러
How shameless are you?
얼마나 뻔뻔한가?
Are you so impatient?
너무 참을성이 없나요?
If you don’t want my identity
내 신분을 원하지 않는다면
Exposed to my leader
내 리더에게 노출됨
Just let me go quickly
그냥 빨리 보내줘
I still have some time to go beforehand
아직 미리 갈 시간이 좀 있어요
Treat you to dinner next week
다음 주에 저녁 식사를 대접하세요
Arrange the interview
인터뷰를 준비하다
Look, you scare people
보세요, 당신은 사람들을 겁주게 해요
I ran away when I saw you.
나는 당신을 보고 도망쳤습니다.
what did she tell you
그 사람이 너한테 뭐라고 말했어?
Invite me for an interview and dinner
인터뷰와 저녁식사에 저를 초대해주세요
That's it
그게 다야
Really let me go
진짜 날 놔줘
Zheng Shuyi, Zheng Shuyi
정수이, 정수이
No matter how good your manuscript is,
아무리 좋은 원고라도
Still being compared to the interns
아직도 인턴이랑 비교되네
A wise man does not fall in love
현명한 사람은 사랑에 빠지지 않는다
Want to wait for me to turn around and speak first
내가 돌아서서 먼저 말하길 기다리고 싶어
is impossible
불가능하다
Don't even think about the feast
잔치 따위는 생각도 하지 마
What are you doing standing there?
거기 서서 뭐해요?
Pray for blessings
축복을 위해 기도하세요
gone
다 쓴
If you walk slowly, I won’t send you off.
천천히 걸으면 보내지 않을 거예요.
send you home
집에 보내줘
Hello
안녕하세요
It is you
그건 너다
Waiting for the bus
버스를 기다리다
Yeah yeah
응 응
There are too many people taking taxis
택시를 타는 사람들이 너무 많아요
I've been waiting for a long time
나는 오랫동안 기다려 왔습니다.
I bought an extra can for you to drink
네가 마실 수 있도록 한 캔 더 샀어
Thanks
감사해요
When my car arrives, I'll leave first.
차가 도착하면 내가 먼저 출발할게.
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
I sent you a text message but you didn’t reply.
문자 메시지를 보냈는데 답장이 없으셨어요.
Give you a rainbow fart and you ignore it
무지개 방귀를 뀌면 무시해
Instead you went to hook up with someone
대신 넌 누군가를 만나러 갔지
see you
또 봐요
A woman who is so nervous that she sweats
땀이 날 정도로 긴장하는 여자
Am I not beautiful enough?
나는 충분히 아름답지 않은가?
Am I not working hard enough?
내가 열심히 일하지 않는 걸까?
Or do you think the president likes it?
아니면 대통령이 좋아한다고 생각하시나요?
Woman, you are afraid of me
여자야, 당신은 나를 무서워해요
This one
이 하나
tacky
초라한
Bad taste
나쁜 맛
But I have
하지만 나는
What position do you blame him for?
당신은 그를 어떤 입장에서 비난합니까?
I'm obviously the one I'm fighting for
나는 분명히 내가 위해 싸우는 사람이다
And he didn't promise anything
그리고 그 사람은 아무것도 약속하지 않았어
Eight ups and downs of emotions in one scene
한 장면에 담긴 여덟 가지 감정의 기복
What
무엇
I said it will rain at eight o'clock tonight
오늘 밤 8시에 비가 올 거라고 했는데
Then will you hold an umbrella for me?
그럼 우산 좀 들어줄래?
Hello
안녕하세요
you say
당신은 말한다
I know, just hang up like this.
알아요, 그냥 이대로 끊으세요.
Then hang up like this first
그럼 먼저 이렇게 끊으세요
Why am I here again?
내가 왜 또 여기에 있는 거지?
You fell asleep in the car
당신은 차에서 잠들었어요
You've been waiting for me for a long time
당신은 오랫동안 나를 기다리고 있었어요
how did you get there
거기 어떻게 갔어요
Don't wake me up either
나도 깨우지 마
soon
곧
It's sour
시큼하다
I mean
내 말은
If you are always free
늘 자유롭다면
I want to treat Shi Zong to a meal
Shi Zong에게 식사를 대접하고 싶습니다
Thank you for taking me home today
오늘 집에 데려다줘서 고마워요
actually
실제로
I happen to have one more thing
우연히 한 가지가 더 생겼어요
want to talk to you
너랑 얘기하고 싶어
That's what I told you last time
그게 내가 지난번에 말했던 거야
that topic
그 주제
If Reporter Zheng wants to date me
정 기자가 나랑 사귄다면
time words
시간 단어
You can contact Chen Sheng
Chen Sheng에게 문의할 수 있습니다.
I have something else to do
다른 할 일이 있어요
Thank you for taking me home
집에 데려다줘서 고마워요
Then I'll go down first
그럼 나 먼저 내려갈게
It was such a good atmosphere just now
지금 분위기 너무 좋았어
What topic should I mention?
어떤 주제를 언급해야 할까요?
Let's go
갑시다
its not right
그것은 옳지 않아
Yunchuang and here are two directions.
Yunchuang과 여기에는 두 가지 방향이 있습니다.
He was so busy and he sent me home
그 사람 너무 바빠서 날 집에 보냈어
He had a busy day at the press conference
그는 기자회견으로 바쁜 하루를 보냈다
He even sent me home specially
심지어 날 특별히 집에 보내줬어
In fact, he is quite considerate.
사실 그는 꽤 사려 깊은 사람이다.
Why don't you come out and walk your dog?
밖에 나가서 개를 산책시키는 게 어때요?
The dog is so cute
개가 너무 귀여워요
Who is she?
그녀는 누구입니까?
I do not know
모르겠어요
etc.
등.
He was concerned about chatting up Qin Shiyue
그는 Qin Shiyue와 대화하는 것에 대해 걱정했습니다.
Come back and take me home again
돌아와서 나를 다시 집으로 데려다주세요
hold my head
내 머리를 잡아
He clearly wanted to
그 사람은 분명히 하고 싶었는데
Two boats
보트 두 척
I'm so angry. I'm so angry.
나 정말 화 났어. 나 정말 화 났어.
never mind
괜찮아요
What kind of good person am I?
나는 어떤 좋은 사람인가?
I also have ulterior motives for him
나도 그 사람에 대한 속셈이 있어
Why should I ask him?
내가 왜 그 사람에게 물어봐야 합니까?
That's right, that's it
그렇구나, 그렇구나
its not right
그것은 옳지 않아
Although I have ulterior motives for him
비록 내가 그 사람에 대해 다른 동기를 갖고 있음에도 불구하고
But I didn’t flirt with anyone else at the same time.
그러나 나는 동시에 다른 사람과 장난을 치지 않았습니다.
Emotionally I feel for him
감정적으로 나는 그 사람을 좋아한다
Is it wholeheartedly okay?
진심으로 괜찮나요?
Hello
안녕하세요
Going out for a drink?
술 한잔하러 나가시나요?
Not going
안 가요
Not coming
안 온다
What are you thinking about?
당신은 무엇에 대한 생각?
I'm thinking
나는 생각 중입니다
Not as good as my man
내 남자만큼 좋지는 않아
You can't marry
넌 결혼할 수 없어
Then I'll marry you
그럼 나 너랑 결혼할게
OK
좋아요
What are you thinking about?
당신은 무엇에 대한 생각?
like us
우리처럼
People who only love freedom
자유만을 사랑하는 사람들
How could there be a wedding day?
어떻게 결혼식 날이 있을 수 있겠습니까?
I don’t know how to
어떻게 해야할지 모르겠어요
Contact that person
그 사람에게 연락해
Is it possible to ask my uncle?
삼촌한테 물어봐도 돼요?
Shi Yan, this stingy guy
시얀, 이 인색한 놈
big pig hooves
큰 돼지 발굽
Why do you like to put on airs so much?
왜 그렇게 방송하는 걸 좋아해요?
He also asked me to make an appointment with Chen Sheng
그는 또한 나에게 Chen Sheng과 약속을 하자고 요청했습니다.
What did my uncle do again?
삼촌은 또 무슨 짓을 한 거야?
Is it a little too much?
조금 너무한가?
mom
엄마
I really don't have time
정말 시간이 없어요
Go see your what?
가서 무엇을 보러 가세요?
The son of an old colleague
옛 동료의 아들
I've already broken up, right?
난 이미 헤어졌죠?
Didn't I tell you?
내가 말하지 않았나요?
between this season
이번 시즌 사이
I still need some time to rest.
아직은 쉴 시간이 좀 필요해요.
OK OK OK
오케이 오케이 오케이
Wait until I'm done with this period of time
이 시간이 끝날 때까지 기다려주세요
I'll do whatever you want
당신이 원하는 건 뭐든지 할게요
I won’t tell you anymore since I’m at work.
회사라서 더 이상 말하지 않겠습니다.
Bye
안녕
Sales of the last issue of the magazine doubled
잡지 마지막 호의 판매량이 두 배로 늘었습니다.
Thank you all for your hard work
모두들 노고에 감사드립니다
keep it up
계속해라
Exclusive interview with Shuyi Na Shiyan
Shuyi Na Shiyan과의 독점 인터뷰
The response is also very good
반응도 너무 좋고
The content of the article is great
기사 내용이 훌륭하네요
Precise and sharp
정확하고 날카로운
It also caused a stir in the circle
서클에도 파문을 일으켰다
great response
좋은 반응
Congratulations on the writing
글을 축하드립니다
achieved such good results
이렇게 좋은 결과를 얻었습니다
I hope everyone can learn from her
모두가 그녀에게서 배울 수 있기를 바랍니다
make persistent efforts
끈질기게 노력하다
good
좋은
calligraphy
달필
You won’t invite everyone tonight
오늘 밤에는 모두를 초대하지 않을 거예요
Let's go out and celebrate together
나가서 함께 축하하자
Yes, Shuyi
응, 슈이
yes
예
calligraphy
달필
Everyone is talking to you
다들 너한테 얘기하고 있어
what does it mean
무슨 뜻이에요
Sister Yuling
율링 자매
are you talking to me
나와 대화하고 있니
Excuse me
실례합니다
I wore noise-canceling headphones
노이즈 캔슬링 헤드폰을 착용했어요
did not hear it
듣지 못했어요
That's it
그게 다야
Everyone is saying that you are frustrated in love
다들 사랑에 좌절했다고 하잖아
Prosperity in the workplace
직장에서의 번영
Wrote such a good manuscript
너무 좋은 원고를 썼어요
Everybody wants you
모두가 당신을 원해요
Treating guests to dinner
손님에게 저녁 대접하기
sure
확신하는
You guys pick a place
너희들은 장소를 골라
Step aside
비켜서 다
So my first day at work
그래서 출근 첫날
Called her several times
그녀에게 여러 번 전화를 했어요
She ignored me
그녀는 나를 무시했다
It's because I wore headphones and didn't hear it
헤드폰을 끼고 있어서 듣지 못했거든요
It's over, it's over
끝났어, 끝났어
I also had a miserable relationship with my uncle
나도 삼촌과 사이가 좋지 않았어
As a result, uncle
그 결과 삼촌은
Made her so miserable
그녀를 너무 비참하게 만들었어
What kind of ancient romance is this?
이것은 어떤 고대 로맨스입니까?
What's the misunderstanding?
무슨 오해가 있나요?
Are you stupid?
너 바 보니?
Uncle, don’t talk.
삼촌, 말하지 마세요.
I'm thinking
나는 생각 중입니다
You can actually think
당신은 실제로 생각할 수 있습니다
Let me ask you something seriously
진지하게 물어보자
if i'm not careful
내가 조심하지 않으면
without knowing it
그것을 모르고
What to do if you become a villain
악당이 된다면 어떻게 해야 할까요?
Do you have the intelligence to be a villain?
당신은 악당이 될 지능을 가지고 있습니까?
you just can't
당신은 할 수 없습니다
Stop squeezing me first, okay?
나부터 먼저 쥐어짜지 마세요, 알았죠?
I just found out today
오늘에서야 알았네요
In fact, I misunderstood my leader
사실 나는 리더를 오해했다.
She didn't ignore me on purpose
그녀는 일부러 나를 무시하지 않았다
What's the meaning
무슨 뜻인가요?
In short it is
요컨대 그것은이다
a misunderstanding
오해
But I'm sorry
하지만 미안해요
Apologize to her
그녀에게 사과하세요
Because she doesn't even know
왜냐면 그 사람도 모르거든
It's me who filed a complaint with you
당신에게 불만을 제기한 사람은 바로 나입니다.
correct
옳은
little uncle
작은 삼촌
Didn’t you make people miserable?
사람들을 비참하게 만들지 않았나요?
Why don't you go find someone and apologize?
가서 누군가를 찾아 사과하는 게 어때요?
If you are a villain
당신이 악당이라면
Opening three minutes
오픈 3분
will be eliminated
제거될 것이다
Help
돕다
I don't really want it
난 별로 그걸 원하지 않아
Go and apologize to people in person.
직접 가서 사람들에게 사과하세요.
I, Qin Shiyue, have lived for twenty-two years
나 진시월은 22년을 살았다
Never hurt anyone else
절대로 다른 사람에게 상처를 주지 마세요
To the point where I have to say sorry to people
사람들에게 미안하다고 해야 할 정도로
This is too embarrassing
이건 너무 부끄러워
It hurts your self-esteem too much
자존심이 너무 상해서
self-esteem
자아 존중감
First you have to be able to get hurt
먼저 상처받을 수 있어야 한다
Qin Shiyue
진시웨
I advise you to hurry up
서둘러야 한다고 조언한다
Solve this matter
이 문제를 해결하세요
People who are otherwise forced to be villains
그렇지 않으면 악당이 될 수밖에 없는 사람들
like me
나처럼
It's also possible that he might actually become a villain
실제로 악당이 될 가능성도 있다.
against you
당신에 대한
Sister Nan
난 자매
Do you have Sister Shuyi’s WeChat account?
Shuyi 자매의 WeChat 계정이 있나요?
you mean
네 말 뜻은
Shi Yan also knew Qin Shiyue
Shi Yan은 Qin Shiyue도 알고 있었습니다.
yes
예
And he cares about her a lot
그리고 그 사람은 그녀에게 많은 관심을 갖고 있어요
this girl
이 여자
So popular
너무 인기가 많아
No wonder she helped you last time
지난번에 그녀가 당신을 도와준 것도 당연해요
Get the invitation
초대장 받기
Her family conditions
그녀의 가족 조건
Should be good too
역시 좋아야지
So we can pass the upper route
그래서 우리는 위쪽 경로를 통과할 수 있습니다.
Go to your magazine
잡지로 이동
Shi Yan and she are both acquaintances
Shi Yan과 그녀는 둘 다 지인입니다.
That all makes sense
다 말이 되네요
I don’t know how familiar I am.
나는 얼마나 친숙한 지 모릅니다.
So you are minding now
그러니까 지금 신경쓰고 있는 거야
The relationship between Shi Yan and her
Shi Yan과 그녀의 관계
Are you jealous
당신은 질투
Jealous
질투하는
no
아니요
but i treat him
하지만 난 그 사람을 치료해
It's a bit interesting
좀 흥미롭네요
are you serious
너 진심이야?
are you sure
확실합니까
What about your topic?
당신의 주제는 어떻습니까?
Like him
그를 좋아하다
People on the cusp of the storm
폭풍의 한가운데에 있는 사람들
If you are really together
정말로 함께라면
We have work contacts again
또 직장 연락처가 있어요
There will definitely be an uproar
분명 난리가 날 것이다
You can tell me everything
당신은 나에게 모든 것을 말해 줄 수 있습니다
and
그리고
You don't remember me before
당신은 전에 나를 기억하지 않습니다
Have I told you about the rumors about him?
그 사람에 관한 소문에 대해 내가 말했습니까?
Was an actress before
예전에 배우였나
Now with your intern
이제 인턴과 함께
unclear
불분명하다
some feelings
어떤 감정
If it is destined not to last long
오래 가지 못할 운명이라면
Might as well not start at all
아예 시작하지 않는 편이 나을 수도 있다
i know what you are thinking
나는 당신이 무슨 생각을하는지 알아요
Things like feelings
감정 같은 것
Just follow your heart
그냥 당신의 마음을 따르십시오
Emotional matters
감정적인 문제
Is it really that simple?
정말 그렇게 간단합니까?
add
추가하다
do not add
추가하지 마세요
No more, no more, no more
더 이상, 더 이상, 더 이상은 안돼
add
추가하다
do not add
추가하지 마세요
Qin Shiyue
진시웨
If you make a little more noise
좀 더 시끄럽게 하면
Just get out of here
그냥 여기서 나가세요
May I ask Miss Song?
송 선생님께 물어봐도 될까요?
You have been in business for so many years
당신은 오랫동안 사업을 해왔습니다.
Have held so many concerts
콘서트를 너무 많이 해서
Then this time
그렇다면 이번에는
25th Anniversary Concert
25주년 기념 콘서트
What's the same as before?
이전과 같은 점은 무엇입니까?
What's the difference?
차이점이 뭐야?
In fact, over the years
사실, 수년에 걸쳐
I think every concert
내 생각엔 콘서트마다
It's all a new beginning
모두 새로운 시작이야
But this year I think
하지만 올해는 내 생각엔
I want to use my singing voice
노래하는 목소리를 사용하고 싶어요
bring all old friends
옛 친구들을 모두 데려와
brought to the past
과거로 가져온
get back those of us
우리를 돌려보내라
Good memories
좋은 기억
So this year I invited
그래서 올해는 제가 초대했어요
The world's top speakers
세계 최고의 스피커
Stage design and lighting team
무대디자인 및 조명팀
I just want everyone to be able to
난 그냥 모두가 할 수 있었으면 좋겠어
While having old memories
옛 추억을 간직하면서
And some new experiences
그리고 새로운 경험들
It makes us look forward to it even more
우리를 더욱 기대하게 만드네요
Almost forgot
거의 잊었다
I originally wanted to grab it
원래는 잡고 싶었는데
I watched it with that dog man
그 개 아저씨랑 같이 봤어
Since he doesn't like to eat
그 사람은 먹는 걸 좋아하지 않아서
Then why not invite him to the concert?
그렇다면 그를 콘서트에 초대해 보는 것은 어떨까요?
Anyway, he also likes Song Lelan
어쨌든 그 사람도 송 렐란을 좋아해요.
No good night today
오늘은 잘 자지 못해
Because I'm very uneasy
왜냐하면 나는 매우 불안하기 때문이다.
I can't sleep now
지금은 잠이 안 와요
If you add me on WeChat
WeChat에 나를 추가하면
I can sleep now
이제 잠을 잘 수 있어요
Mr. Shi
시 씨
You also like Song Lelan
송렐란도 좋아하시네요
coincidence
우연의 일치
I like her very much too
나도 그녀를 아주 좋아해요
I have all these albums
나 이 앨범 다 갖고 있어
Which of her songs do you like best?
그녀의 노래 중 어떤 노래를 가장 좋아합니까?
completion
완성
Is it too much?
너무 많은가요?
SY
SY
banquet
연회
He finally added me on WeChat
그 사람이 마침내 나를 WeChat에 추가했어요
I won and he responded to me.
내가 이겼고 그는 나에게 응답했습니다.
Quite girlish
꽤 소녀스러운
It’s the suffix that follows
뒤에 오는 접미사입니다.
A bit coquettish
약간 요염함
Only available for three days
3일간만 이용 가능
Quite mysterious
꽤 신비한
It's also like his style
그 사람 스타일이랑도 비슷해요
I finally waited until you added me on WeChat
드디어 네가 나를 위챗에 추가할 때까지 기다렸다
Are you going to sleep
자러 갈 건가요?
Just saw this
방금 이걸 봤어
Who are you thinking of going with?
누구랑 갈 생각이야?
are you free tomorrow night
내일 밤에 시간 있어?
Then let's go together tomorrow night
그럼 내일 밤에 같이 가자
We actually got an appointment so smoothly
사실 우리 약속이 너무 순조롭게 잡혔어
Is Shi Yan changing his gender?
Shi Yan이 성별을 바꾸나요?
I would like to ask Miss Song
송 선생님에게 묻고 싶습니다.
You have been in business for so many years
당신은 오랫동안 사업을 해왔습니다.
Have held so many concerts
콘서트를 너무 많이 해서
So this time the twenty-fifth anniversary
그럼 이번에는 25주년
The concert is the same as before
콘서트는 예전과 똑같아
What's the difference?
차이점이 뭐야?
Want to watch a concert together?
콘서트 같이 볼래?
But didn’t Sanmao say that?
그런데 산마오가 그런 말을 하지 않았나요?
if you don't like
당신이 좋아하지 않는다면
Millionaires don’t marry either
백만장자들도 결혼하지 않는다
if you like
당신이 좋아한다면
Multimillionaires also marry
억만장자도 결혼한다
Things like feelings
감정 같은 것
Just follow your heart
그냥 당신의 마음을 따르십시오
I have free media tickets here
여기 무료 미디어 티켓이 있어요
Do you want to go see it together?
같이 보러 갈래?
See you then
그때 만나
Tomorrow afternoon
내일 오후
Do you have time to play golf?
골프 칠 시간 있나요?
Unsubscribe
구독 취소